CONTACT INFORMATION



vice 012@hotmail.com



WhatsApp +52 2226581419 Mobile: +52 2217041087



https://www.linkedin.com/i n/vicente-cortes-9a293a1a6/



https://github.com/aurox1000

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- > Web developer
- Scrum and Prototyping
- Mobile Development
- ▶ BDD/BD
- Empathy
- Initiatives to hang out with the team
- Cybersecurity

STRENGTHS

Adaptability Problem solving Proactivity Teamwork Communication

IT Engineer

Vicente Cortes Hernández

I am an IT engineer, familiar with a wide range of utilities and languages. I have experience in C#, Python and JavaScript. I am used to work with cross-cultural and global teams collaboratively, I would like to learn new technologies and improve professionally.

WORK EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVELOPER | Criteria Inteligencia de negocios September.2022 |- actually.

- > Website development, design.
- Backend(php, python, c#)
- > Frontend(html5, bootstrap, css3.
- > BDD(oracle, MySQL Database. SQL Server)

RESIDENT ENGINEER | ASIATECH S.A de CV.

February. 2020 - June. 2020.

- > Professional residence in the area of software development.
- > Prototyping and XP methodology.
- > Front end and backend in C#, Visual Studio IDE, Bunifu Framework.

SUPPORT TECHNICIAN | INSTITUTO TECNOL OGICO NACIONAL DE MEXICO.

Agust. 2019 - December. 2019

- > Social service in the computer and systems department.
- > Preventive and Corrective Hardware and Software Maintenance
- Network monitoring

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

Instituto tecnológico nacional de México 2014-2020 Specialization in business intelligence strategies.

Cisco Networking Academy

Currently studying Cybersecurity, Programming, Networking, IOT, OS: Linux Ubuntu.

ILearningX-Huawei

Currently studying Artificial Intelligence, Cloud Computing, Programming.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Personal Portfolio https://aurox1000.github.io/portafolio-/